A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Telephone Directory FA234
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Telephone Directory
1958-2002
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
Rockefeller University
FA234
0.95 Cubic Feet 3 boxes
3 boxes.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 457
Scope and Contents
The Telephone Directory of the Institute/University lists the names, telephone numbers, mail box numbers, and office/lab location of academic and non academic staff. An alphabetical index of "Offices and Services" is listed at the end of each directory.
Arrangement
Chronological
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Medical education
- Telephone directory, 1958-2002
  - Rockefeller Institute, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller Institute, 1960-1962 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller Institute/University, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller University, 1966-1968 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller University, 1971-1972, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller University, 1973-1974 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller University, 1975-1976 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller University, 1977-1978 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller University, 1979-1980 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller University, 1981 October (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Scope and Contents
    Preliminary edition
  - Rockefeller University, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller University, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller University, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller University, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller University, 1988 July (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller University, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller University, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Rockefeller University, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Rockefeller University, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Rockefeller University, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller University, Spring 2002 (Box 3, Folder 2)